Trying the popcorn that has become a
cultural heritage here in Rio de Janeiro.
It's very generously filled, folks.  I'm dying to
eat.  Come on,
guys!  We'd always heard about this
popcorn, the most famous in Rio, and today
we came to try it.  We arrived late, it's
almost closing time,
but we'll have time to eat.
But that's just how we are, isn't it?  Hey, we might be
late, but we'll be there.
We always arrive.
We do a bad job, but we do it.
That's what matters.  The important thing is to do it.
What are the most popular flavors here?   They
all come in the little bag.  How do you
see it in the bucket?  Ah, everyone here is in the
bucket.  And we can order something like shrimp
with added cheese.
I need to add it.  You can put cheese
here, you understand?
Ah, okay then.  So
[clearing throat] we'll have
these two Kinder Bueno ones and the shrimp
with cheese.  That guy over there is the one who talks to
us about the 20s.
So it could be the 20s. So,
is the K-ban still around or is it over?
Oh no, music has to have people, it has to
have K downloaded.
I'll have this one, but it's the one from...  You can
add Nutella if you like.  So what
changes is the Kinder Bueno topping.  And
Kinder Bueno.  If he wants, he can use the
same syrup, just changing the biscuit.
Could it be.  Do you have any other cookies besides the
train?   Yes, it does
.  It could be horrible.  I prefer it.   It
could be, but
it's just crumbly.
All good.  We arrived late, did
n't we?  What time do you open here?  1 hour.   It
stays open until 9. It's been
made especially for you, okay?
Is it hazelnut cream or is it real Nutella
?
Hazelnut cream.  This one here is the famous
Nutella flavor.  [laughs]
So we'll finish up here by putting
more popcorn for you.
And this is Kinder cream.   It
's no coincidence that we get a
cultural dish, right?   Cool
.  The best popcorn in Rio de
Janeiro.  Today we are 23 units.
I think I've only ever seen you guys making
popcorn like this before.
The best popcorn in Rio is made by us.   Has
anyone tried to do something similar outside of
Rio?
No. Our plan is to expand
throughout Brazil.  You think it's
over?  It's not over.   Just
when you think it's over, he keeps
adding more.
Thank you very much, young lady.
Passaldar.  Pass and have a blast.
Let's start with the savory
shrimp and cheese fritters.  There's plenty of
shrimp.
There are a lot of shrimp.  I'm going to eat the
shrimp now.
I'll get one.  Hmm. Hmm, very tasty.
What a nicely seasoned, delicious little shrimp!
And does the popcorn taste like shrimp?
It's perfect.
The oil ends up making the popcorn a little less
crispy.  There are some pieces of
cheese, they're kind of fried, you see?
Hmm. Very salty.  But I'm hot.
Oh, but I like it.  I like
salty things, you know?
Let's give it a rating.  I loved.
I loved this popcorn.  I loved this
shrimp.  Delicious.  Eat it all up
.
You nailed it, Mr. Manna.  Now sweet.  Guys,
it's so stuffed that it's almost hard
to eat.  That's why they give those little blows.
Look at my hand.  A little bit of oil,
thank God.
Wow, this is so beautiful, isn't it
?  Let's prove it.  This is Kinder cream
.
Oh
my God.  My God.  Very good.
Wow, [clearing throat] that's
delicious.
This popcorn is very good.   There
must be 500,000 calories in here, but it's worth it
.
I keep weighing the weather.  [laughs]
And this one stays crunchy because it's
sweet popcorn, right?  My God.  Very good, my
friend.  I loved it here.   Uh-huh
.   Uh-huh
.
Perfect.  This is in a movie.
Our.  And a bottle of water.  And
a bottle [laughs] of water.  10 out of 10. It was worth it
.  It was well worth it.  It's
totally worth the hype.  It's very tasty.  And now
we're going to finish eating, okay?
Kiss.